Mike Wallace Papers
Mike Wallace Papers
- Interview audiorecordings
  - Col. Gregory "Pappy" Boyington, Bert Wheeler, Huntington Hartford, James Roosevelt, Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr., Mel Allen, wallace_m_248; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 7)
  - Gen. James van Fleet, Anne Bancroft, Eva Gabor, Gus D’Amato, Julie Newman, Toots Shor, David Susskind (fragment), wallace_m_249; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 7)
  - Tom Poston, Ben Cohn, Jolie Gabor, Gerry Mulligan, Fred Demara, Mrs. Theodore Roosevelt, David Susskin (fragment), wallace_m_250; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 7)
  - Arlene Francis, Frank O’Leary, Rudy Vallee, Averell Harriman, Peter Ustinov, Terry Danielsen, wallace_m_251; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 7)
  - Edmund Hillary, Dr. Alan Guttmacher, Jane Bloeth, Ed Hilgemeier, George Jessel, wallace_m_252; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 7)
  - Dorothy Day, Eddie Bracken, Harold Medina, Betty Furness, Cab Calloway, Rona Jaffee, wallace_m_253; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 164:25 (Oversize 8)
  - Meyer Levin, Bill Stern, William Laurence, Cornelia Otis Skinner, Wally Cox, Raoul Levy; all with commercials; “Newscast @ end of side b ‘Newsbreak’” “Van Doren/ Dance Party”, wallace_m_254; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 171:20 (Oversize 8)
  - Dennis O’Keefe, Melvyn Douglas, “Joe,” juvenile gang leader (incomplete), Nina Foch, Flair Coles, Abe Burrows, wallace_m_255; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 164:51 (Oversize 8)
  - Katina Paxinor, Francis Harwich, Conrad Nagel, Bob Cousy, John Crosby, Geraldine Page, wallace_m_256; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Emmet John Hughes, Leonard Sillman, Otto Preminger, Victor Riesel, Joe Pasternak and James B. Carey, wallace_m_257; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 166:51 (Oversize 8)
  - Harrison Salisbury, Moss Hart, Krishna Menon, Denise Darcel, Hildegarde and Howard Edmondson, wallace_m_258; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Leo Rosten, Norman Mailer, Bennett Cerf, Mae Murray, Sam Dash and Erskine Caldwell; 6 separate shows on 1 reel, wallace_m_259; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips (Oversize 8)
  - Maurice Evans, Beverly Aadland, Theodore Bikel, A. Phillip Randolph, Amy Vanderbilt and Shirley MacLaine, wallace_m_260; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Roy Campanella, Buddy Rich, Admiral Elmo Hutchinson, Ramon Navarro and Cleveland Amory, wallace_m_261; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Gus Hall, Stanley Isaacs, Inger Stevens (2 parts), Chester Bowles, Joachim Prinz and Herbert Lehman, wallace_m_262; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Henry Sherek, Ed Fitzgerald, Robert Wagner, Paul Blanchard [Blanshard?], Pat Hingle and Diana Barrymore, wallace_m_263; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Dr. Fredric Wertham, Stanley Kramer, Bill Veeck, Mike Todd Jr., Ken Murray and Frank Lane, wallace_m_264; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; six separate interviews, total running time 164:20 (Oversize 8)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright (Parts 1 & 2), wallace_m_265; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; running time 56:09 (Oversize 8)
  - Lorraine Hansberry, wallace_m_266; reel tape, 1/4", 3 3/4 ips; running time 29:18 (Oversize 8)
  - Lorraine Hansberry, wallace_m_267; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Christine Jorgensen, wallace_m_268; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Harry Ashmore, wallace_m_269; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Jacqueline Cochran, wallace_m_270; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Fred Demers, wallace_m_271; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - William Douglas, wallace_m_272; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Cyrus Eaton, wallace_m_273; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Erich Fromm, wallace_m_274; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Robert Hutchins, wallace_m_275; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Aldous Huxley, wallace_m_276; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Henry Kissinger, wallace_m_277; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - George Jessel, wallace_m_278; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Francis Lally, wallace_m_279; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Reinhold Niebuhr, wallace_m_280; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Charles Percy, wallace_m_281; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Sylvester Weaver, wallace_m_282; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright and Julie Newman, wallace_m_283; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Profiles of Marilyn Monroe, Harry Belafonte, Carl Sandburg, Sammy Davis Jr., Tony Curtis, Jack Paar, Liz Taylor, Frank Sinatra, Zsa Zsa Gabor, Dean Martin, wallace_m_284; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - James Baldwin, Mischa Jac Feld, wallace_m_285; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Anthony Quinn, wallace_m_286; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Ashley Montagu and David Susskind (part 1 of 2), wallace_m_287; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
  - Jean Seberg and Ayn Rand (fragment), wallace_m_288; reel tape, 1/4" (Oversize 8)
- The Hate That Hate Produced (documentary)
  - Transcript and binder of miscellaneous material (Box 12)
  - Telecine (Reel 1 of 2), wallace_m_291; 16mm film, black and white, sound (Oversize 9)
  - Telecine (Reel 2 of 2), wallace_m_292; 16mm film, black and white, sound (Oversize 9)
  - VHS (Copy 1), wallace_m_289; Videotape, VHS (Box 13)
  - VHS (Copy 2), wallace_m_290; Videotape, VHS (Box 13)
Index to interviews
The following is an alphabetical list of all interview participants as well as a few notable individuals who were the subject or topic of intervews (e.g., Winston Churchill). Each name is followed by a list of the script(s) and/or recording(s) available in the collection. Note that all audio interviews have been digitized.
Aadland, Beverlyscript, Nov 10 1959 recording, undated
Aherne, Brianscript, Apr 1 1960 recording, undated
Albee, Edward script, Feb 15 1961
Albert, Eddiescript, Jan 17 1961 recording, undated
Allen, Melscript, May 12 1959 recording, undated
Allen, Stevescript, Oct 10 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Amory, Clevelandscripts, Dec 10 1959, Dec 5 1960, Dec 19 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Andrews, Danascript, Apr 6 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Anka, Paulscript, Nov 22 1960 recording, undated
Ashmore, Harryscript, May 19 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Atkinson, Tedscript, Mar 4 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Aumont, Jean Pierrescript, Mar 10 1960 recording, 3/17/1960
Axelrod, Georgescripts, Mar 30 1960, Apr 20 1960 recording, undated
Baldwin, Jamesscript, Mar 24 1961 recording, undated
Balin, Inascript, Sep 13 1960 recording, undated
Bancroft, Annescript, Mar 6 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Barrymore, Diana recording, undated
Baxley, Barbarascript, Nov 21 1960 recording, undated
Bean, Orsonscript, Mar 18 1959 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Beatty, Clydescript, Apr 9 1959 recording, undated
Bedford, Duchess ofscript, Oct 25 1960 recording, undated
Begin, Menachemscript, Nov 28 1960 recording, undated
Belafonte, Harryrecording, undated recording, undated
Belfrage, Sallyscript, Mar 23 1959 recording, undated
Bendix, Williamscript, Oct 31 1960 recording, undated
Bennett, Tonyscript, Mar 29 1961 recording, undated
Berman, Shelleyscript, Apr 20 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Bikel, Theodorescript, Nov 20 1959 recording, undated
Blanchard, Paul [Blanshard?] recording, undated
Blansherd, Paul [Blanshard?] script, Jan 14 1960
Block, Martinscript, Mar 12 1959 recording, undated
Bloeth, Janescript, Aug 17 1959 recording, undated
Bonomi, Johnscript, Dec 20 1960 recording, undated
Boswell, Conneescript, Dec 19 1960 recording, undated
Bowles, Chesterscript, Dec 17 1959 recording, undated
Boyington, Gregory "Pappy" (Colonel)script, May 5 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Bracken, Eddiescript, Sep 16 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Bradley, William (Captain)script, Apr 13 1959 recording, undated
Branden, Nathanielscript, Feb 29 1960 recording, 3/18/1960
Bricktopscript, Mar 3 1961 recording, undated
Brooks, Melscript, Jan 17 1961 recording, undated
Bucholz, Earlscript, Feb 9 1961 recording, undated
Buckley, William F. Jr.scripts, Dec 5 1960, Feb 29 1960 recording, 3/7/1960 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Burnett, Carolscript, Mar 17 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Burrows, Abe recording, undated
Caldwell, Erskinescript, Nov 6 1959 recording, undated
Calloway, Cabscript, Sep 24 1959 recording, undated
Calvert, James (Captain)script, Nov 1 1960 recording, undated
Campanella, Royscript, Nov 27 1959 recording, undated
Carey, James B.script, Oct 29 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Carnera, Primoscript, Mar 10 1961 recording, undated
Carroll, Diahannscript, Feb 10 1961 recording, undated
Cassevetes, Johnscript, Oct 31 1960 recording, undated
Cassini, Olegscript, Jan 6 1961 recording, undated
Cater, Douglass script, Oct 4 1960
Cerf, Bennettscript, Nov 19 1959 recording, undated
Channing, Carolscript, Mar 3 1961 recording, undated
Charell, Lissascript, Apr 1 1960 recording, undated
Chase, Ilkascript, Oct 10 1960 recording, undated
Churchill, Winston (subject of interview)recording, undated recording, undated
Clyde Beatty recording, undated
Cobb, Lee J.script, May 10 1960 recording, undated
Cochran, Jacqueline recording, undated
Cohen, Alexander script, Dec 4 1959
Cohen, Benjaminscript, Jun 17 1959 recording, undated
Cohn, Ben recording, undated
Coles, Flair recording, undated
Comden, Bettyscript, Feb 17 1961 recording, 2/17/1961
Conniff, Frankscript, Jan 6 1961 recording, undated
Conreid, Hansscript, Feb 24 1959 recording, undated
Cousy, Bobscript, Sep 16 1959 recording, undated
Cowles, Fleur script, Oct 15 1959
Cox, Wallyscript, Oct 5 1959 recording, undated
Crawford, Christinascript, Sep 19 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Crawford, John script, Aug 17 1959
Crawford, Kenneth script, Nov 7 1960
Crosby, Garyscript, Mar 23 1961 recording, undated
Crosby, Johnscripts, Oct 28 1959, Nov 7 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Crowther, Bosleyscript, Apr 3 1960 recording, undated
Cugat, Xavierscript, Mar 30 1959 recording, undated
Curtis, Tony recording, undated
D'Amato, Gusrecording, undated script, May 12 1959
Dahl, Roaldscript, n.d. recording, undated
Danielsen, Terryscript, Jul 23 1959 recording, undated
Darcel, Denisescript, Nov 4 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Darin, Bobbyscripts, May 31 1960, Mar 16 1961 recording, undated recording, undated
Dash, Samscript, Nov 4 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Dauphin, Claudescript, Mar 3 1960 recording, 3/11/1960
Davis, Mrs. Sammy Jr. recording, undated
Davis, Sammy Jr.scripts, Mar 2 1959, Dec 28 1960 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, March 9-13, 1959 recording, undated
Day, Dorothyscript, Sep 9 1959 recording, undated
Dayan, Moshe recording, undated
Dee, Rubyscript, Mar 30 1961 recording, undated
DeHaven, Gloria script, Nov 14 1960
Demara, Fredscript, Jul 7 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Demers, Fred recording, undated
Desai, Morarjiscript, Oct 4 1960 recording, undated
Diller, Phyllisscript, Oct 17 1960 recording, undated
Douglas, Jackscript, Apr 6 1959 recording, undated
Douglas, Melvynscript, Oct 9 1959 recording, 1960 recording, undated
Douglas, William recording, undated
Downs, Hughscript, Sep 12 1960 recording, undated
Duchamp, Marcelscript, Dec 12 1960 recording, undated
East, P.D.script, Mar 10 1961 recording, undated
Eastman, Max script, Apr 13 1959
Eastman, May recording, undated
Eaton, Cyrusrecording, undated recording, March 9-13, 1959 recording, undated
Eban, Abba recording, undated
Ed Fitzgerald recording, undated
Edmondson, J. Howardrecording, undated script, Oct 26 1959
Ellis, Albert (Dr.)script, Mar 26 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Emerson, Fayescript, May 30 1960 recording, undated
Evans, Mauricescript, Nov 20 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Fabianscript, Sep 26 1960 recording, undated
Falkenberg, Jinxscript, Aug 24 1959 recording, undated
Feiffer, Julesscript, Mar 30 1960 recording, undated
Feld, Mischa Jac recording, undated
Fitzgerald, Ed script, Jan 8 1960
Fletcher, Josephscript, Oct 3 1960 recording, undated
Foch, Ninascript, Oct 12 1959 recording, undated
Ford, Philscript, Jan 12 1961 recording, undated
Francis, Anne script, Sep 15 1959
Francis, Arlenescript, Feb 24 1959 recording, undated
Francis, Conniescript, Nov 16 1960 recording, undated
Frank, Gerald [Gerold?] recording, undated
Frank, Gerold script, Mar 18 1959
Fromm, Erich recording, undated
Furness, Bettyscripts, Oct 1 1959, Mar 10 1961 recording, undated recording, undated
Gabor, Evascript, Jun 10 1959 recording, undated
Gabor, Joliescript, Jul 2 1959 recording, undated
Gabor, Zsa Zsascript, Feb 9 1961 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, 1959
Galento, Tonyscript, May 1 1959 recording, undated
Gang leader, unnamed script, Sep 30 1959
Gardner, Hyscript, Apr 22 1959 recording, undated
Gerlich, Jackie script, May 1 1959
Gifford, Frankscript, Mar 9 1961 recording, undated
Gillespie, Dizzyscript, Mar 23 1961 recording, undated
Gloria DeHaven recording, undated
Goldberg, Ruberecording, undated recording, undated
Gonzalez, Panchoscript, Apr 15 1959 recording, undated
Graham, Sheilahscript, Feb 23 1959 recording, undated
Granville, Josephscript, Dec 12 1960 recording, undated
Gray, Robertscript, Feb 3 1961 recording, undated
Greco, Josescript, Apr 15 1960 recording, undated
Green, Adolphscript, Feb 17 1961 recording, 2/17/1961
Greene, Gaelscript, Apr 17 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Gregory, Dickscript, Apr 10 1961 recording, undated
Griffin, John Howardscript, Mar 22 1960 recording, undated
Griffith, Andyscript, May 5 1959 recording, undated
Guttmacher, Alanscript, Jul 29 1959 recording, undated
Haigh, Kennethscript, Mar 10 1960 recording, 3/23/1960
Hall, Gusscripts, Dec 17 1959, Jan 6 1961 recording, 1/5/1961 recording, undated
Hansberry, Lorrainescript, May 8 1959 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Hardwicke, Sir Cedricscript, Apr 2 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Harriman, Averellscript, Jul 27 1959 recording, undated
Hart, Mossscript, Oct 28 1959 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Hartford, Huntingtonscript, May 12 1959 recording, undated
Harwich, Francis recording, undated
Hauser, Gayelordscript, Jan 26 1961 recording, undated
Havoc, Junescript, Feb 25 1959 recording, undated recording, March 9-13, 1959
Hayakawa, Sessuescript, Apr 20 1959 recording, undated
Hecht, Benscript, Mar 23 1959 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Hildegardescript, Nov 5 1959 recording, undated
Hilgemeier, Edscript, Aug 10 1959 recording, undated
Hillary, Sir Edmundscript, Aug 3 1959 recording, undated
Hines, Mimiscript, Jan 12 1961 recording, undated
Hingle, Patscript, Jan 14 1960 recording, undated
Hodges, Lutherscript, Apr 14 1961 recording, undated
Hoffman, Richardrecording, undated script, Feb 21 1961
Horwich, Frances script, Sep 16 1959
Hughes, Emmet Johnscript, Nov 5 1959 recording, 1959 recording, undated
Huie, William Bradfordscript, Mar 16 1959 recording, 3/24/1960
Humphrey, Hubertscript, Mar 9 1959 recording, undated
Hunter, Kimscript, Apr 30 1961 recording, undated
Hutchins, Robert recording, undated
Hutchinson, Elmo (Admiral)script, Dec 10 1959 recording, undated
Huxley, Aldous recording, undated
Irwin, Monte script, Mar 14 1960
Isaacs, Stanleyscript, Dec 23 1959 recording, undated
Jackie Gerlich recording, undated
Jackson McVey recording, undated
Jaffe, Ronascript, Sep 21 1959 recording, undated
Jessel, Georgescript, Aug 31 1959 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Joe (juvenile gang leader; maybe pseudonym) recording, undated
Jorgensen, Christinescript, Apr 22 1959 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Kenny, Nickscript, Oct 30 1960 recording, undated
King, Dennisscript, Mar 2 1961 (?) recording, undated
King, Martin Luther Jr.script, Feb 2 1961 recording, undated recording, undated
Kinkead, Eugenescript, Mar 18 1959 recording, undated
Kintner, Earlscript, Feb 16 1960 recording, undated
Kissinger, Henryscript, Mar 2 1961 recording, undated recording, undated
Kitt, Earthascripts, Jun 17 1959, Apr 14 1961 recording, undated
Kline, Nathanscript, Mar 10 1960 recording, 3/25/1960
Koch, Leorecording, undated script, Nov 16 1960
Kramer, Stanley recording, undated
Kukla recording, undated
Laine, Frankiescript, Apr 15 1959 recording, undated
Lally, Francis recording, undated
Lanchester, Elsascripts, Aug 31 1959, Feb 23 1961 recording, undated
Landis, James M. (Jim)script, Jan 11 1961 recording, 1/11/1961
Lane, Abbescript, Mar 30 1959 recording, undated
Lane, Frankscript, Jan 24 1960 recording, undated
Lanphier, Thomasscript, Jun 2 1960 recording, undated
Laurence, Williamrecording, undated recording, undated scripts, Oct 2 1959, May 30 1960
Laurie, Piperscript, Jan 24 1960 recording, undated
Lehman, Herbertrecording, undated script, Dec 30 1959
Lemmon, Jackscript, Oct 31 1960 recording, undated
Leonard, Jack E.script, Mar 25 1960 recording, undated
Leonetti, Tommyscript, Mar 23 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Lerner, Maxscript, Oct 10 1960 recording, undated
Levin, Meyerscript, Sep 28 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Levy, Raoulscript, Sep 23 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Leyra, Camilo Westonscript, Apr 2 1959 recording, undated
Liloscript, Nov 14 1960 recording, undated
Lomax, Louis recording, undated
London, Ephraimscript, Apr 28 1959 recording, undated
Loos, Anitascript, Apr 6 1961 recording, undated
Lorre, Peterscript, Feb 17 1960 recording, 3/8/1960
Louis, Joescript, May 26 1960 recording, undated
Louise, Tinascript, Mar 2 1960 recording, 3/9/1960
Lovejoy, Frankscript, Apr 14 1960 recording, undated
Loy, Myrna script, Oct 17 1960
Lumet, Sidney script, Feb 25 1960
Lynley, Carolrecording, undated script, Mar 3 1961
Lytess, Natashascript, Nov 21 1960 recording, undated
MacDonald, Jeanette script, Aug or Sept 1959
Machado, Chinascript, Mar 21 1961 recording, 3/2/1961
MacLaine, Shirley script, Nov 23 1959
Maclver, Joyce script, Feb 3 1961
Mailer, Normanscript, Nov 18 1959 recording, undated recording, 11/21/1960 recording, undated
Malden, Karlscript, Mar 17 1961 recording, undated
Mankowitz, Wolfscript, Mar 16 1960 recording, 3/31/1960
Mannes, Maryascripts, Apr 3 1960, Oct 25 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
March, Halscript, Mar 9 1961 recording, undated
Martin, Dean recording, undated
Mason, Pamela (Mrs.James Mason)script, Dec 26 1960 recording, undated
Maurois, Andrescript, Nov 16 1960 recording, undated
Maxwell, Elsarecording, undated script, Apr 14 1961
McBride, Mary Margaretscript, Dec 13 1960 recording, undated
McDonald, Mariescript, Apr 6 1959 recording, undated
McDowell, Roddyscript, Apr 14 1961 recording, undated
McIver, Joyce recording, undated
McKay, Gardnerscript, May 19 1960 recording, undated
McManus, Virginia script, n.d.
McVey, Jackson script, Apr 3 1960
Meacham, Annerecording, undated script, Nov 28 1960
Meadows, Jaynescript, Mar 26 1959 recording, undated
Medina, Haroldscript, Sep 2 1959 recording, undated
Meir, Golda recording, undated
Menon, V. K. Krishnarecording, undated recording, undated script, Nov 6 1959
Merriam, Evescript, Nov 7 1960 recording, undated
Merrick, Davidscript, Jan 12 1961 recording, 1/11/1961
Mesta, Perlescript, Apr 14 1960 recording, undated
Meyer, Frankscript, Jan 5 1961 recording, undated
Michelfelder, Williamscript, Oct 3 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Michener, Jamesscript, Sep 27 1960 recording, undated
Mineo, Salscripts, May 10 1960, Sep 19 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Monroe, Marilyn (subject of interview) recording, undated
Montagu, Ashleyscript, Sep 13 1960 recording, undated
Mr. John [?]script, Apr 28 1959 recording, undated
Muggeridge, Malcolmscript, Sep 26 1960 recording, undated
Mulligan, Gerryrecording, undated recording, undated script, Jul 1 1959
Murray, Kenscript, Feb 11 1960 recording, undated
Murray, Maescript, Nov 18 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Myerson, Bessscript, Oct 18 1960 recording, undated
Myrna Loy recording, undated
Nagel, Conradscript, Oct 16 1959 recording, undated
Navarro, Ramon recording, undated
Newman, Julierecording, undated recording, undated
Newman, Paul recording, undated
Newmar, Julie scripts, Apr 15 1959, Feb 23 1961
Nichols, Mikescript, Dec 20 1960 recording, undated
Niebuhr, Reinhold recording, undated
Novarro, Ramonscript, Nov 27 1959 recording, undated
O'Brien, Margaretrecording, undated script, Mar 9 1961
O'Keefe, Dennisscript, Sep 15 1959 recording, undated
O'Leary, Frankscript, Jul 9 1959 recording, undated
Obolensky, Serge (Colonel)script, Mar 30 1959 recording, undated
Odero-Jour, J.G. script, Nov 16 1960 (?)
Ollie the Dragon recording, undated
Paar, Jack recording, undated
Page, Geraldine recording, undated
Pasternak, Josephrecording, undated recording, undated script, Oct 30 1959
Pauling, Linusrecording, undated script, Oct 24 1960
Paxinou, Katinarecording, undated script, Oct 5 1959
Percy, Charles recording, undated
Pernot, Dom Placide (Father)script, Sep 19 1960 recording, undated
Petrovskaya, Kyrascript, May 8 1959 recording, undated
Pike, James (Bishop)recording, undated script, Feb 21 1961
Pincus, Gregoryrecording, undated script, Nov 22 1960
Poston, Tomscript, May 22 1959 recording, undated
Powell, Adam C. script, Mar 16 1959
Preminger, Ottoscripts, Jun 23 1959, Jan 12 1961 recording, undated recording, 1/12/1961 recording, undated
Prinz, Joachimscript, Jan 8 1960 recording, undated
Pruell, Clayton recording, undated
Quill, Michael J.scripts, Apr 22 1959, Sep 26 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Quinn, Anthony recording, undated
Rand, Aynscripts, Feb 25 1959, Apr 18 1960, Mar 17 1961 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, March 9-13, 1959 recording, undated
Randall, Tony script, Sep 2 1959
Randell, Ron script, Aug 5 1959
Randolph, A. Philiprecording, undated script, Oct 21 1959
Regler, Gustavscript, Mar 3 1960 recording, undated
Remick, Lee scripts, Aug 26 1959, Jan 27 1960
Reuther, Walterscript, Oct 4 1960 recording, undated
Reynolds, Quentinscripts, Sep 27 1960, n.d. recording, undated recording, undated
Rich, Buddyscripts, Sep 3 1959, Dec 6 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Riesel, Victorscripts, Oct 23 1959, Dec 28 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Ritchard, Cyrilscript, Apr 14 1961 recording, undated
Robbins, Lewis L. (Dr.)script, Feb 10 1961 recording, 2/10/1961
Robustelli, Andyscript, Apr 11 1961 recording, undated
Rocca, Antoninoscript, Apr 22 1960 recording, undated
Rodgers, Richard recording, undated
Roosevelt, Franklin D. Jr.recording, undated script, May 25 1959
Roosevelt, Mrs. Theodore (Eleanor Butler Alexander-Roosevelt)script, Jul 24 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Roosevelt, Jamesscript, May 25 1959 recording, undated
Rosenfeld, Henryscript, Nov 8 1960 recording, undated
Rosensohn, William script, Jun 23 1959
Rosten, Leoscript, Oct 7 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Roth, Philipscript, Mar 28 1960 recording, undated
Ruark, Robert script, Sep 1959 (?)
Rule, Janicescript, Apr 11 1961 recording, undated
Sahl, Mortscript, Apr 6 1960 recording, 4/6/1960
Salisbury, Harrisonscript, Oct 22 1959 recording, undated
Sandburg, Carlscript, Sep 12 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Schary, Dorescript, Mar 16 1961 recording, undated
Scopes, John T. script, Oct 10 1960
Scott, Hazelscript, Apr 14 1961 recording, undated recording, undated
Scott, Zacharyscript, Feb 2 1961 recording, undated
Seal, Elizabethscript, Jan 12 1961 recording, 1/12/1961
Seberg, Jeanrecording, undated script, Mar 17 1961
Segal, Harry "Champ"script, Feb 15 1961 recording, 2/15/1961
Serling, Rod script, Sep 15 1959
de Seversky, Alexander P.recording, undated script, Apr 22 1960 recording, undated
Sheean, Vincentscript, Mar 7 1960 recording, 3/16/1960
Sherek, Henryscript, Dec 30 1959 recording, undated